fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
What?!
O-Oh!
T-That's...
It's the empty shell of sand!
Hot-blooded Dropout!
Finally
Unleashed,
the Forbidden
Master Move!
When did that...?!
That's not possible!
While you had your eyes closed
and were praying.
What?
For a moment, Lee stopped moving
because of the pain in his body.
At that moment... that's when!
Gaara!
That's...!
There's no doubt about it – his eyes...
He's completely awake...
The demon... inside him.
Run away!
That Bowl-Cut's totally worn down...
Gaara is toying with him.
W-Why doesn't Lee-san dodge?
With Lee-san's speed, he should easily be
able to dodge that level of attack.
It's not that he doesn't dodge,
it's that he can't dodge.
What?!
What do you mean?
The Lotus is a double-edged sword.
What do you mean double-edged sword?
Why do you think the Lotus is
a forbidden technique?
Well...
The Lotus isn't a Ninjutsu or a Genjutsu.
It's a Taijutsu, with that much
high-speed movement.
The load it puts on a person's body
is beyond imagination.
So Lee's entire body is in
so much pain right now
that even moving is out of the question.
Isn't that so...
Guy?
But that's...!
He has no Ninjutsu, not even
one Genjutsu...
Moreover, the Taijutsu he depends on,
it's now even less than
an average person's...
There's no way he can win!
He's had it if this goes on...
Lee...
Hey, get a move on all of you.
I'll add another 200 laps!
Stupid! There's no way
you'll become a Ninja.
Yes, I will.
There's no way a chump who can't
even use Ninjutsu can become a Ninja!
Yes, I will!
Whatever, but the fact that a guy like
you without Ninjutsu or Genjutsu
and with less Taijutsu than
an average person
is in this Ninja academy is nonsense.
Do you know what you're called here?
Hot-Blooded!
Hot-Blooded lose-
Hey, get in line, Lee!
Hey, Lee!
So that's the hot-blooded loser
everyone's talking about.
Doesn't he look like
someone we know?
Huh?
In particular... his eyebrows.
Hmm...
Rock Lee...
The chump who can only perform
less than average Taijutsu...
But you...
You practiced your less
than average Taijutsu...
You practiced it over and
over again like crazy...
396... 397... 398... 399...
400... 401... 402... 403...
If I can't do a log kick 500 times,
then it's 1,000 squats!
413... 414...
415... 416... 417... 418...!
419... 420...
So someone's here before me...
422... 423... 424...
425... 426...
I suppose I'll come back...
If I can't do 1,000 squats,
then it's 2,000 punches!
795... 796... 797... 798...
He's still at it...!
2,000 punches!
If I can't, it's 2,000 jump ropes!
You recklessly practiced only
Taijutsu and eventually...
All right, you've all become
Genin as of today,
so I'd like to know what
it is you're all aiming for!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Tenten.
I'd like to become a powerful Ninja
like the legendary Kunoichi, Tsunade-sama!
Hmm...
And, how about you, Neji?
I don't want to answer...
I...!
I'd like to prove that I could
become a respectable Ninja
even though I can't use
Ninjutsu or Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
Those are good serious eyes...
— Humph!
— You!
What's so funny?!
I'm serious!
I will become a respectable Ninja
even only with Taijutsu!
He should give up already...
At this rate...
He will simply die with Gaara
just toying with him...
Bushy Brows...!
Lee...
Not yet... Not yet!
Lee, you just won't learn
your lesson, will you?
There's no way you can win...
Unlike you, Neji is a genius.
A genius...?
What is a genius?!
Even though I may not have talent,
I'll exceed genius with my efforts.
That is my entire being!
That is my Ninja Way!
You'll get nowhere, Lee...
No matter how much effort you make,
there's no way you can take me down.
That's simply a fact.
That's not true!
That's not...
But you... refused to give up, not ever!
Such meaningless actions...
The Bowl-Cut was unlucky to
have Gaara as his opponent!
No...
Lee's not one to give up
with this much.
— What?
— Huh?
The reason is that Lee...
You... continued to make effort.
If I can't jump rope 1,200 times,
I'll log kick 2,000 times!
1,116... 1,117...!
1,118... 1,11...!
Huh?!
Lee!
Are you taking a break already?
Guy-sensei...
What is it that you want?
If it's about my blunder with
the recent assignment,
I believe I've apologized.
Lee... It's true you're different from Neji.
You have no Ninjutsu or Genjutsu skills,
and you're not a Taijutsu genius either...
But Lee...
you have powers
that exceed Neji...
you're a genius with hidden potential.
If you're trying to make me feel better,
please stop!
Idiot!
I'm not trying to make you feel better
or anything!
The reason is that you are...
a genius of effort!
I wonder if...
If that's true...?
I've... I've believed that to be true...
That if I trained harder than Neji...
2 or 3 times as much...
that I'd surely become stronger.
But...
I've recently begun to think that...
I can't beat a real genius.
Is effort really rewarded...?
I've wanted to know this and
so I've taken on Neji,
but it's always been the same...!
I'm no match for him at all!
Even when I'm on a mission...
My legs still tremble even now...
I think that I'll never become
stronger though I strive and strive...
I am so afraid that I can't bear it!
What am I to do...?
There's no point in making the effort
if you don't believe in yourself!
Lee, you're very similar to me.
Do you mean our eyebrows?
No, not just our eyebrows...
I was actually a failure once too...
You were, Sensei?
But now, I can even win against
the genius elite Kakashi,
because of my efforts...
"I'd like to prove that I can become
a respectable Ninja
even though I can't use Ninjutsu
and Genjutsu" you said.
That's your Ninja Way, right?
That's a fine goal...
It's a fine goal worth sticking to!
That's why you should believe in
your path and forge straight ahead!
Become a man powerful enough
so that I can just watch you smiling!
Understand, Lee?!
Yes!
Thank you... Guy-sensei...!
Stop, Lee-san!
If you fight any more, you'll die!
Bushy Brows...
What?!
Movement has...
...returned to Lee!
Sensei is smiling and watching me...
And just because of that,
I can come back stronger!
Stronger... stronger still!
Lee-san's smiling... even though
he's been driven into a corner.
No.
It's his turn to do the driving.
Huh?
The Leaf's Lotus blossoms twice.
Blossoms twice...?
Lee-san said that too!
The Leaf's Lotus blossoms twice.
When we meet the next time,
I vow that I will be an even stronger man.
No, Guy!
You haven't?!
It's exactly as you imagine.
So that Genin...
that boy can open the Eight Inner Gates
in his body and use the Hidden Lotus...
The Hidden Lotus?
That's right...
This is incredible...
Guy...
How many of the Eight Inner Gates
can that boy open now...?
Five gates.
What exactly is it?
These Eight Inner Gates and
that Hidden Lotus?
The Eight Inner Gates are
"Limiter Releases"
used in preparations for
reaching the Hidden Lotus.
A "Limiter Releases"?
That's right...
In the Chakra Network
where chakra flows,
there are eight places where the
chakra points are concentrated
in each area of the body from the
head area down...
Opening
Rest
the Gate of Opening, Gate of Rest,
Gate of Life, Gate of Pain,
Life
Pain
Closing
Joy
Gate of Closing, Gate of Joy,
Gate of Shock and Gate of Death.
Shock
Death
These are called the Eight Inner Gates.
These eight gates
continually "limit"
the amount of Chakra flowing
through the body...
However, the Lotus's essence is to force
the boundaries of these "limits" to open...
and bring out several
tens of times the body's strength.
The Primary Lotus...
opens only the first gate,
the Gate of Opening,
and releases the brains restraints
to bring forth a person's muscles' strength
to its fullest!
That's the kind of technique it is.
So... what is the Hidden Lotus?
After forcing the stamina to increase
at the second gate, the Gate of Rest...
From the third gate, the Gate of Life,
one enters the Hidden Lotus!
No way!
Even after using just the Primary Lotus,
his body was in shambles.
So if he uses a technique beyond that...
That's right.
Huh?
By opening all the 8 gates,
one attains strength exceeding
even the Hokage, but in return...
one dies!
I don't intend to pry into what that
boy means to you
or to tell you not to bring
your personal feelings into play...
But there is a limit!
I've misjudged you... Guy!
What do you know... about that boy?!
There is something important which
that boy wants to prove and
protect even if it costs him his life.
I'd like to prove that I can become
a respectable Ninja
even though I can't use
Ninjutsu and Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
That's why I...
wanted to make him a man
that could protect that thing.
That's all there is...
Lee!
I'm going to teach you
a new technique.
Yippie, yeah!
— One that will be your trump card.
— Yeah, that's great!
Yippie, yeah! Yippie yeah!
Lee, listen to my explanation
seriously, all right?!
Y-Yes, Sensei!
Let me first say that...
this is more of a forbidden Jutsu
than the Primary Lotus!
And it will become the
most special technique for you.
Special...?
However...
there is one strict condition
for using this technique.
That is...
What?
I don't know what
you're planning to do...
But this is the end for you.
That's true...
In any case...
it will be the end with the next.
Neji...
Sasuke-kun... and...
There is no way that I alone
can lose in a place like this!
Guy-sensei... please allow this...!
It is now!
The time to carry through and
protect one's own Ninja Way!
The Third Gate of Life... open!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
Effort is always rewarded.
My belief in this has brought me this far.
Neji, Sasuke-kun, and Naruto-kun...
There's no way that I can lose
in a place like this!
Even though this technique is
my ace in the hole,
I'll show it especially to you!
This is my ultimate secret
Taijutsu technique!
Next Episode:
"Ahh, Rock Lee! This is How a Man Should be!!"
This is the end!